ANASTASIYA KULAGINA

Amsterdam, the Netherlands | +31 623 74 96 84 | a.kulagina19@gmail.com

- Working rights in The Netherlands
- Working remotely within international teams
- 2,5 years in business and IT recruitment and 2 years of experience in HRIS

Being a passionate HR professional specializing in project management, process improvements and recruitment, I have a track record of successfully building and optimizing processes, launching HR projects, managing stakeholders needs and strengthening teams with top-notch candidates.

I bring strong communication and interpersonal skills, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities, along with the skill to create an engaging environment and effectively contribute to reaching business goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TESLA Amsterdam, the Netherlands

HR Process Specialist

January 2023 - current

- Conducted monthly system trainings for new joiners in the HR department
- Designed a new knowledge base on Sharepoint for the HR Operations team and created a guideline for the content migration
- Created process roadmaps and conducted discovery sessions for Benefits automation in EMEA countries
- Was the sole representative from the OPEX team to support troubleshooting for Benefits/Outflow/Out-of-Office teams
- Held UATs for system enhancements

<u>Termination reason</u>: Hiring freeze within the team with no possibility to extend a fixed-term contract.

COCA-COLA HBC Moscow, Russia

HR Manager

September 2021 - June 2022 Conducted monthly system trainings for new joiners in the HR department

- Led digitization project of an onboarding program on Articulate Rise and optimized 4% working hours per month for this activity
- Collaborated with the L&D team and helped in the creation of training materials
- Collaborated with EMEA Digital Support team and coordinated nationwide implementation project of a new ATS
- Facilitated Operation plan's workshop for recruitment
- Held monthly team meetings and prepared 15+ presentations for stakeholders
- Led a project of Power BI implementation in recruitment team of 30 and supported them with the hiring platforms
- Successfully organized main processes in recruitment and optimized 1,5% working time (50 hours) for TA team
- Owned OPEX budget for recruitment and saved 10% on spending on external contractors
- Led 3 projects in Employer branding division

Termination reason: Relocation from Russia to the Netherlands.

HSE GRADUATE SCHOOL OF BUSINESS

Moscow, Russia

September 2020 - August 2021

April 2020 - September 2020

HR Process Manager

- Held more than 50 career consultations
- Led a large project of building all internal processes in the Career Center from scratch
- Created a tiered course «Start your successful career» with videos and 12 guides for students
- Created commercial presentations of the Center services, quarterly presentations for stakeholders
- Created a process of obligatory practice with useful materials and connected it with platform provider
- Negotiated with group of stakeholders and defined their needs
- Researched a market for the best practices
- Presented the Career Center at the Open House

Termination reason: It was a project-based assignment, and there was no further development plan after the processes were created and launched.

TOCHKA BANK Yekaterinburg, Russia

IT Recruiter

- Was responsible for hiring UX designers, analysts, frontend and backend developers (Java, Go)
- Made nationwide screening and developed a map of regional key companies
- Expanded the funnel of candidates by posting vacancies in relevant Telegram channels
- Identified a blind zone and created a single template for tests developing the HR brand collaboratively with SME
- Updated recruitment Knowledge base in Confluence

Termination reason: Relocation from Yekaterinburg to Moscow.

YANDEX (YANGO) Yekaterinburg, Russia

Recruiter November 2018 – April 2020

- · Was responsible for hiring managers, analysts and department heads in the business unit
- Managed the stakeholders' expectations and needs regarding candidate profiles
- · Collaborated on analytical database for hiring in Google Spreadsheets
- Proposed a development plan consisting of 8 projects aimed at optimizing existing business processes
- Developed and implemented a training and adaptation program for new employees of the business recruitment team of 23 from scratch

<u>Termination reason</u>: Due to Covid-related downsizing of staff and hiring freeze.

HIGHER SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS

Yekaterinburg, Russia

Educational Programs Coordinator

September 2017 – November 2018

- Organized and controlled the whole learning process for trainers and students
- Created and hold a course «Typology of body shapes and styles»
- Managed up to 6 educational groups of 15-20 people simultaneously
- · Supported and negotiated between students and trainers
- Prepared all educational documentation
- Presented the School at program launches

Termination reason: To start my career in HR and gain experience in recruitment.

URAL FEDERAL UNIVERSITY

Yekaterinburg, Russia

Academic department Coordinator / Project Coordinator

October 2014 - August 2017

- Assisted in developing academic programs for bachelor's and master's degree students
- Helped revise academic curricula for audits
- · Organized department meetings and managed the tracking of faculty work hours
- Collected and checked all documents of foreign students for the project «Russian Studies in Real Russia»
- Organized their outdoor activities
- Controlled the student's safety and supported them in critical situations

EDUCATION

Ural Federal University (NUST "UrFU")
Bachelor Linguistics and international communication

Yekaterinburg, Russia 2013 – 2017

Ural Federal University (NUST "UrFU")

Professional retraining in Human Resources

Yekaterinburg, Russia 2016-2017

SKILLS & PERSONAL

Languages: German (basic), English (fluent), Russian (native)

IT: Figma, Power Point, Miro, Excel, Articulate Rise, Confluence, Slack, Asana, Trello, Power BI, Huntflow, Cornerstone, SAP, MS

Sharepoint, Wix

Soft skills: Result-oriented, Self-structured, Open-minded, Team player